(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-13T02:37:41.691491",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
始まってしまったからには やるしかないでしょがい！
Now that it's begun, we've got no choice but to do it!
ほら、私たちのチャンネルは…
Look, our channel is...
スバちょこるなたん スバちょこるなたん スバちょこるなたん 始まるよ～！
SubaChocoLunaTan, SubaChocoLunaTan,
SubaChocoLunaTan, it's starting!
地獄で会おうぜ！ スバちょこるなたん
See you in hell! SubaChocoLunaTan
地獄から来たスバちょこるなたん 地獄で会おうぜ！
SubaChocoLunaTan from hell, see you in hell!
地獄で会おうぜ！ 地獄で会おうぜ！
See you in hell! See you in hell!
ちわー！スバちょこるなたんのツッコミ担当！どんなボケも切り捨てるごめん！恐怖の極卒マネージャー大空スバルだー！
Hello! I'm Subaru Oozora, the terrifying
prison guard manager!
ちょこ！スバちょこるなたんの限界担当！地獄を燃やす点々の点滴！恐怖の極卒保健医癒月ちょこだー！
I'm Choco Yuzuki, the terrifying
prison nurse!
ばぶー！スバちょこるなたんのバブ担当！悪魔も出る甘えの天才！恐怖の極卒お姫様姫森ルーナなんだななのらー！
I'm Himemori Luna, the terrifying
prison princess, nananora!
はーい！スバちょこるなたんのゲラ担当！どんな極効も成功で恐怖の極卒ホリィキャノン獅白ぼたんだー！
I'm Shishiro Botan, the terrifying
prison sniper!
今日のお迎えはどんなかな？正気のうちに覚悟しな！ 咲いて咲くそうじごくの空気で…
I wonder what kind of greeting awaits us today?
Prepare yourself while you're still sane!
ま、じ、ご、く、 へい お待ち！
Tr-u-e he-ll, hey, we've been waiting!
チャンネル回転今何時？ こちらは一対一、一期一会！
What time is it on the channel rotation?
Here it's one-on-one, once-in-a-lifetime!
生のせいで地獄の釜をふるーえ！そしたらいいじゃんこの感じ！
Because of life, shake the cauldron of hell!
Then isn't this feeling great?
遠くの天国より 金魚の地獄前向けば無限の娯楽！
Farther than heaven, facing the goldfish hell,
infinite entertainment!
振り向けばこの手から来る 目指せ爆笑俺たちにとよんで！
Turn around and it comes from this hand,
aim for a riot of laughter, call us—!
スバちょこるなたん スバちょこるなたん スバちょこるなたん 始まるよ～！ 始まるよ～！！
SubaChocoLunaTan, SubaChocoLunaTan,
SubaChocoLunaTan, it's starting!
地獄から来たスバちょこるなたん 地獄で会おうぜ！
SubaChocoLunaTan from hell,
see you in hell!
地獄に落ちるぞ 地獄はいいぞ ここが地獄かお邪魔します！
You'll fall into hell, hell is great,
is this hell? Pardon the interruption!
ぶんだー！なんだなのらこの音符！全員クソ雑魚なんだのら！
Bunda! What are these notes, nanora?
You're all total weaklings, nanora!
ほらダンス！ちょっとガチ勢！ねえ見て見て！地獄に最大1匹の点々！
Hey dance! A bit serious!
Hey look look! At most 1 dot in hell!
もうやめろやめろ！地獄なんだよな！
Stop it already! It's hell, isn't it!
チャンネル回転今何時？ こちらは一対一、一期一会！
What time is it on the channel rotation?
Here it's one-on-one, once-in-a-lifetime!
生のせいで地獄の釜をふるーえ！
Because of life, shake the cauldron of hell!
あいじまうよ♪
Let's start playing♪
地獄！地獄！今日も地獄！地獄から来た
Hell! Hell! Hell again today! Coming from hell,
スバちょこるなたん！
It's SubaChocoLunaTan!
地獄！地獄！いつでも地獄！
Hell! Hell! Hell anytime!
地獄で会おうぜ♪ スバちょこるなたん！
Let's meet in hell♪ SubaChocoLunaTan!
ちゃーっす！スバちょこるなたんのツッコミ担当！
What's up! The straight-man of SubaChocoLunaTan!
どんな小ボケもリスーそごめん！
I catch every little joke, sorry!
恐怖の獄卒マネージャー、大空スバルだーーーっ！
The terrifying warden manager, Oozora Subaruーー!
(スバル！スバル！シュバシュバシュバスバル！)
(Subaru! Subaru! Shuba-shuba-shuba-Subaru!)
ちょこん♪ スバちょこるなたんの限界担当！
Choko♪ The limit-breaker of SubaChocoLunaTan!
地獄をも癒やしてぇぇの伝道師！
The evangelist who heals even hell!
恐怖の獄卒保健医、癒月ちょこでーーす！
The terrifying warden nurse, Yuzuki Chocoーー!
(ちょこ！ちょこ！ちょこちょこちょこさき！)
(Choko! Choko! Choko-choko-choko-saki!)
ん、なーーーっ！スバちょこるなたんのダブ担当！
N, naaーー! The mooch of SubaChocoLunaTan!
悪魔もでれる甘えの天才！
The genius of spoiled cuteness that even demons fawn over!
恐怖の獄卒お姫様、姫森ルーナなのだーーーっ！
The terrifying warden princess, Himemori Lunaーー!
(ルーナ！ルーナ！んなんなるーな！)
(Luna! Luna! Nna-nna-Luna!)
はーーい！スバちょこるなたんのゲラ担当！
Haa-i! The giggler of SubaChocoLunaTan!
どんな愚行も全肯定！
Fully accepting of any foolishness!
恐怖の獄卒鬼教官、獅白ぼたんでーーす！
The terrifying warden drill instructor, Shishiro Botanーー!
(ぼたん！ぼたん！ラ・ライーーオン！)
(Botan! Botan! La-Liiion!)
不安除く your voice 甘くときめいたノイズ
Dispelling anxiety with your voice, a sweetly throbbing noise
脳内暗示 like a sweet candy
Brainwashing like a sweet candy
偉大な愛の暴動 計画なき犯行
A grand riot of love, a planless crime
生命の猛威 gimme your candy
The fury of life, gimme your candy
二人きりだけの世界 what do you wanna do? 重なるlive
A world of just the two of us, what do you wanna do? Overlapping live
キミの息侵され we can fly ah…
Invaded by your breath, we can fly ah...
受け入れて完全な crime there's no lies 裸の愛
Accept it, a total crime, there's no lies, naked love
魅惑 1.2.3 キミを単純に
Fascination 1.2.3, simply taking you
奪い去ってしまう衝動 理性との共謀
An impulse that carries you away, complicity with reason
can you feel もっと感情に
Can you feel it, deeper into emotion?
強く触れて壊して 乱run乱
Touch me hard and break me, run wild
キミと 1.2.3 ずっと eyes on me
With you 1.2.3, always eyes on me
speed up 止まらない鼓動 キセキとの共存
Speed up, unstoppable heartbeat, coexistence with a miracle
close to me もっと深くにおちて down…
Close to me, falling deeper down...
健全な存在証明 必要ないのさ no way
A wholesome proof of existence? No way, you don't need it
欲しがってしまう意味 i my me 甘い甘い candy
The meaning of craving it, i my me, sweet, sweet candy
震え止まない症状 禁断のアレそう more
Symptoms of unending tremors, the forbidden stuff, more
全身の歓喜 let’s start！ you and me
Full-body ecstasy, let's start! You and me
遡る視線のバイブ 鳴り響く野望のチャイム
A vibe of retro-gazing, the chiming of ringing ambition
キミに触れ その瞬間 over drive
Touching you, that moment over drive
「いらない 全部はいらない」なんて言わないで you could be mine
Don't say "I don't need it, I don't need any of it," you could be mine
誘惑 1.2.3 キミが最高に
Temptation 1.2.3, you are at your best
連れ去ってしまう頂点 飛び越えた想像
The peak that carries us away, imagination surpassed
ride on me さぁ you're going to be
Ride on me, now you're going to be
共に果ててしまうまで down…
Down until we perish together...
向かう先は all the night
Heading towards all the night
手に入るタイム so 甘い
Time in our hands, so sweet
きらびやかな日々
Glittering days
意味ギミー その candy
Meaning, gimme that candy
震える生命 and daybreak
Shivering life and daybreak
we stay 永遠 game
We stay in an eternal game
手に入れた その瞬間 気付いて
Realize that moment when we got it
交わる想い 始まる in your way
Intertwining feelings, starting in your way
繰り返し目を合わせた先で
Beyond our repeatedly meeting eyes
弾け飛ぶ世界は in my way
The bursting world is in my way
キミを手に入れる そう it's time
Getting you, yes it's time
中指を立てた この合図
Raising my middle finger, this signal
魅惑 1.2.3 キミを単純に
Fascination 1.2.3, simply taking you
奪い去ってしまう衝動 理性との共謀
An impulse that carries you away, complicity with reason
can you feel もっと感情に
Can you feel it, deeper into emotion?
強く触れて壊して 乱 run 乱
Touch me hard and break me, run wild
キミと 1.2.3 ずっと eyes on me
With you 1.2.3, always eyes on me
speed up 止まらない鼓動 キセキとの共存
Speed up, unstoppable heartbeat, coexistence with a miracle
close to me もっと深くにおちて down…
Close to me, falling deeper down...
魅惑 1.2.3 キミを単純に
Fascination 1.2.3, simply taking you
奪い去ってしまう衝動 理性との共謀
An impulse that carries you away, complicity with reason
can you feel もっと感情に
Can you feel it, deeper into emotion?
強く触れて壊して 乱 run 乱
Touch me hard and break me, run wild
キミに触れ その瞬間 気付いて
Realize that moment when you touch me
交わる想い 始まる in your way
Intertwining feelings, starting in your way
繰り返し目を合わせた先で
Beyond our repeatedly meeting eyes
弾け飛ぶ世界は in my way
The bursting world is in my way
キミを手に入れる そう it's time
Getting you, yes it's time
中指を立てた この合図
Raising my middle finger, this signal
魅惑 1.2.3 キミを単純に
Fascination 1.2.3, simply taking you
奪い去ってしまう衝動 理性との共謀
An impulse that carries you away, complicity with reason
can you feel もっと感情に
Can you feel it, deeper into emotion?
強く触れて壊して 乱 run 乱
Touch me hard and break me, run wild
キミと 1.2.3 ずっと eyes on me
With you 1.2.3, always eyes on me
speed up 止まらない鼓動 キセキとの共存
Speed up, unstoppable heartbeat, coexistence with a miracle
close to me もっと深くにおちて down…
Close to me, falling deeper down...
魅惑 1.2.3 キミを単純に
Fascination 1.2.3, simply taking you
奪い去ってしまう衝動 理性との共謀
An impulse that carries you away, complicity with reason
can you feel もっと感情に
Can you feel it, deeper into emotion?
強く触れて壊して 乱 run 乱
Touch me hard and break me, run wild
キミと 1.2.3 ずっと eyes on me
With you 1.2.3, always eyes on me
ということで、本日は癒月ちょこ生誕祭にお越しいただき、ありがとうございます！
With that said, thank you so much for coming to Yuzuki Choco's birthday celebration today!
今回のハッシュタグはこちら！「#癒月ちょこ生誕祭2024」
Today's hashtag is right here! "#YuzukiChocoBirthday2024"
みんないっぱい呟いてってくださーい。後でご本人にいきます。
Everyone, please tweet lots and lots. I'll be checking them out later.
そして、みんなー！
And everyone!
見て見て、このステージ、すごくないですかー？
Look, look! Isn't this stage amazing?
わーい！
Yay!
はい、今回はね、なんと……こちら！ジャジャーン！
Yes, this time, guess what... right here! Ta-da!
禁断の果実テーマのライブになっておりまーす！
It's a live show themed around the forbidden fruit!
まあ、最後にね、重大告知とかもあるので、皆様お楽しみをー！
And well, at the end, there'll be some major announcements too, so everyone please look forward to it!
そして……皆様、さっき聴いていただいた1曲目、地獄で会おうぜスバちょこルナたーん！
And... everyone, the first song you just heard, "See You in Hell, SubaChocoLuna-tan!"
ただいま絶賛こちら……（画面）配信中でございまーす！
is currently being broadcast right here!
まあね、スバちょこルナたんのわちゃわちゃって感じが存分に味わえる楽曲なので、ぜひぜひ皆様……よろしくお願いします！
Well, it's a song where you can fully enjoy that bustling SubaChocoLuna vibe, so everyone... please check it out!
そして2曲目残したんもね、ちょこの魅力がいっぱい……
And for the second song left, Choco's charm is full of...
伝わったんじゃないかしら？
didn't it come across?
ということで、この後も……お楽しみにお楽しみ……お楽しみに！
With that said, look forward to what's coming next too!
いくぞ！
Let's go!
時には噛んだりして
Bite down from time to time,
痛みを覚えさせて
let me remember what pain feels like.
溢れるエキタイで汚してよ 全部
Stain my entirety with that overflowing fluid.
足の先からずーっと
Right from the tips of my toes,
蹲ったその神経はもう
those crouching nerves are already
感覚に溺れ
drowning in sensation—
身体ココロを連れて
taking my body and heart along!
指くわえた我慢の中
In a patience where I bit my finger,
欲しってんのが理想?
is what I desire an ideal?
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, don't need it at all,
磨き上げてる邪魔なPRIDE
a shined-up obtrusive pride.
無意味な世界のルールくらい
As for the rules of this meaningless world,
無駄としか言い様がない
it's pointless to describe them.
隠しているあなたのSTYLE
Your style is hidden away,
剥き出しにあるがままDIVE
but dive in with it all laid bare.
そこに生まれるのは期待
What's born there is hope,
外れなんかじゃない
it's not a mistake at all—
頂上のSMILE
the smile at the peak!
吐息を合わせた相性
Matching the pace of our breathing,
耳に吹きかける感情
feeling your breath upon my ear,
破裂しそうな胸騒ぎだす細胞
cells going berserk in a bursting heart.
脱ぎかけてるシャツを
Stripping off this shirt,
優しく裂いてよ
kindly rip it apart,
まず かまわず get
first, without a care, get...
フライングも有り 躊躇わないで darlin'
flying is fine too, don't you hesitate, darlin'!
自由な世界の中
In the middle of a free world,
夢見てんのが本性?
is what you're dreaming of your true nature?
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, don't need it at all,
怖気づいた野望のTRY
it's a try born of timid ambition.
満足なんてそこにない
Satisfaction is surely not there,
目に見える哀れな未来
in that clearly miserable future.
思い通りにできるLIFE
Live life as you please,
手にできるかはあなた次第
making it your own depends on you.
隠したりなんかはしない
Don't bother hiding anything,
誰よりも誇らしげにできるMIND
live with a mind prouder than anyone.
ホラこの世界の中 他にはない
Look, in this world, there is nothing else;
確かなもの 自分以外は皆無
the only certain thing is yourself.
小さくなって場合じゃない
There's no time to shrink back,
いつだって No Time!
at any time, no time!
ALL RIGHT 上限値超え
All right, surpass your upper limits,
エンジン全開でいっちゃえ BURN BURN BURN
engines full throttle, let's go burn burn burn!
欲しがってんのはそう 気持ちいいのmore...
What you want, yes, is more of that great feeling...
あるがままの想いでDANCE!
so dance with your raw feelings,
イイナリでGET DOWN!
and get down as you're told!
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, don't need it at all,
磨き上げてる邪魔なPRIDE
a shined-up obtrusive pride.
無意味な世界のルールくらい
As for the rules of this meaningless world,
無駄としか言い様がない
it's pointless to describe them.
隠しているあなたのSTYLE
Your style is hidden away,
剥き出しにあるがままDIVE
but dive in with it all laid bare.
そこに生まれるのは期待
What's born there is hope,
外れなんかじゃない
it's not a mistake at all—
頂上のSMILE
the smile at the peak!
ホラこの世界で今
Right now in this world,
解き放って
let them be free—
鋭くギラつかせた希望
your sharp, dazzling hopes!
もっと本気出していいよ
You can put your all into it even more!
いっそ塵になって転がってたいけど
Even if I'd rather just turn to dust and roll around,
みっともないから口から出る「大丈夫」
since it's pathetic, "I'm okay" slips from my mouth.
透明な街をすり抜け 傷跡晒したままで
Slipping through the transparent town, leaving my scars exposed,
耳障り メトロのメロディ こんな僕も肯定して
a grating metro melody, affirm someone like me too.
感情も 心臓も 値段がつくらしいね
It seems even emotions and hearts get a price tag, huh?
エンドレスな 新規リスナー いくらですか 幸せとは
Endless new listeners, how much is happiness?
かみさま うざったい恥を捨てたら 並べた嘘にキスしよう I love u
Oh God, if I cast away this annoying shame, let's kiss the aligned lies, I love you.
最低辺の楽園さ 孤独と指絡ませ アデュー、サロース
The lowest paradise, intertwining fingers with solitude, adieu, salauds.
何者でもない僕を 責めて慰めてよ アデュー、サロース
Blame and comfort me, who am nobody at all, adieu, salauds.
簡単なことでも絆に息を止めて歩いた
Walking and holding my breath over bonds made of simple things,
愛くるしいあの子はいつの間にか笑えなくなっちゃった
that adorable girl before I knew it couldn't smile anymore.
まだ泣いてんだ この人生は 曇り模様 晴れ間探し 強いってわけじゃない
Still crying, this life is cloudy, searching for breaks in the clouds—it's not that I'm strong.
誰か僕を見てよ 見つけて
Someone, look at me, find me!
うざったい恥を捨てたら 並べた嘘にキスしよう I love u
If I cast away this annoying shame, let's kiss the aligned lies, I love you.
承認に飢えた亡霊さ 負け惜しみで叫んだ アデュー、サロース
A ghost starving for validation, I shouted in defiance, adieu, salauds.
何者でもない僕を 慰める奴はいない アデュー、サロース
There's nobody to comfort me, who am nobody at all, adieu, salauds.
私とStep Step Yeah 今夜はバラ色
Me and Step Step Yeah, tonight is rose-colored,
何重をも乗せて 踊りましょう
let's put on layers and dance!
レンダーステップ 狂いたい 知りたい 隠した想い 月が綺麗なロマンティック
Render step, wanting to go crazy, wanting to know, hidden feelings, a romantic moonlit night.
宵には甘く濡れた果実のように 君にそっとささやくの
Softly whispering to you like fruit wet with the sweetness of evening.
情熱のそそぐままに 踊れ Oh Yeah 本当の素顔を見せて
Just as passion pours, dance Oh Yeah, show me your true face.
もっとキミキミが キミキミが 私の全てを
More, you, you, you, you, all of me...
だって クレイジー クレイジー ロック クレイジー クレイジー ロック 本気で見せてあげる
Because it's crazy crazy lock, crazy crazy lock, I'll show you for real.
あぶらかたまぶら あぶらかたまぶら
Abracadabra, abracadabra,
君と出会えた奇跡に 愛を込めて踊りましょう
let's dance with love for the miracle of meeting you.
いつだって笑って 悩んで 迷える日々も なんて素敵なドラマチック
Always smiling, worrying, even days of getting lost—what a wonderful dramatic.
そうやって探って 感じて 重ね合わせて 君にちょっと近づくの
Searching like that, feeling, overlapping, getting a little closer to you.
鼓動が叫ぶ黒いオーラ
A black aura where my heartbeat screams.
わたしと take a step yeah
Take a step with me, yeah...
今宵はバラ色 night
Tonight is a rose-colored night.
夢をのせて 踊りましょう
Let's dance with our dreams aboard.
なんてったって
After all,
触れたい 知りたい 隠したい想い
I want to touch, know, and hide my feelings.
月が綺麗ね、ロマンティック
The moon is so lovely, romantic.
時には甘く熟れた果実のように
Sometimes like a sweet, ripe fruit,
キミにそっと囁くの
I gently whisper to you.
情熱の誘うままにねぇ
As passion invites, hey,
本当の素顔見せて
show me your true face.
もっと give me gimme love！
Even more, give me, gimme love!
私の全てを
All of me,
だって crazy in love
because I'm crazy in love.
本気魅せてあげる
I'll show you my true seriousness.
アブラカタブラ
Abracadabra
キミと出逢えた奇跡に
To the miracle of meeting you,
アブラカタブラ
Abracadabra
愛を込めて 踊りましょう
let's dance with love!
いつだって
Whenever it is,
笑って悩んで迷う日々も
even in days of smiling, worrying, and wandering,
なんて素敵なドラマティック
how wonderfully dramatic.
そうやって探して感じて重ね合わせて
That's how we search, feel, and overlap,
キミにちょっと近づくの
getting a little closer to you.
鼓動が叫ぶくらいほら本能で強く惹かれて
Look, my heartbeat cries out, strongly drawn by instinct—
そうよ
that's right!
give me gimme love！
Give me, gimme love!
溶かしてあげるわ
I'll melt you away.
きっと fall in love...
Surely fall in love...
need you 止められないの
Need you, I can't stop it.
アブラカタブラ
Abracadabra
こんな素晴らしい世界に
Into such a wonderful world,
アブラカタブラ
Abracadabra
キミのために踊りましょう
let's dance for you!
魅惑を隠す箱 秘宝に香る危なげな
A box hiding allure, fragrant with dangerous treasure—
dangerous marine smell
I'm Your Treasure Box
誘うガーネットの赤 極上の海賊の秘宝
Garnet red of temptation, the ultimate pirate's treasure,
それは私
that is me.
艶が溢れ漂う香りをどうかしょーがいないで開けてみて
Don't fear the scent overflowing with allure, just open it up!
sexy世界一 superピチピチ
Sexy world-number-one, super peachy-peachy,
ぶっちぎり船長捕まえたくない？
wouldn't you want to catch the runaway captain?
you're gonna get the treasure maybe tasting me
秘密の鍵を 優しく刺して
Gently twist the secret key inside,
宝庫の扉マジで早く開けて！
open the vault door for real, quickly!
じれったい貴方の手 海図にこぼす甘いため息 tease
Your impatient hands, sweet sighs spilled on the chart to tease...
純紅のバラがしおれる前に
Before the crimson roses wither,
we will sail the seven seas
summer sun smiling with glee
shining ocean of marine
now, please grant my dearest dream
open up this box open it right now, or i will scream
泣く子も黙る naughty 悩殺ビーム キミたちもう我慢できない？
Silencing even crying children, a naughty captivating beam—can you guys not hold back anymore?
ahoy! don't go! 秘宝の鍵を
Ahoy! Don't go! The key to the treasure,
ahoy! don't go! 優しく刺して
ahoy! don't go! gently thrust it in,
ahoy! don't go! 開けっ放しの扉
ahoy! don't go! the wide-open door!
マジで早く開けて！
Open it up for real, quickly!
切れた大半 あなたの手 隠すにこぼす 溜め息吐息のkiss
Torn halves of your hands, spilling sighs and breathless kisses,
七つの大海を 股にかけ進め
Spanning the seven seas, pressing forward!
踏みにじり また見失ってさ
Trampling over and losing sight of them again...
シャリオ シャリモリ まさか後ろから取り戻しての
Chariot, Shari-Mori, taking it back from behind unexpectedly—
プリンセス型 まんざらでもない
Princess type, not half bad at all!
open at this box, open it right now, oh i wish
i will scream, 錆びのマークじゃ
I will scream, with rust marks—
まだ曇るな 裸のスピリット
Don't cloud over yet, naked spirit!
キミたちももう我慢できなくなって
Can you guys not hold back anymore either?
魅惑を隠す箱
Hiding allure in a box
秘宝に香る
Fragrant with hidden treasure
危なげな
Dangerous...
dangerous marine smell
❤Ahoy❤
Ahoy!
これ開けたら君たちになんて言ってあげるべきかな…？
If I open this, what should I say to you all...?
「探してたのはせ・ん・ちょ・お？」
"Were you looking for Sen-cho?"
うーん…
Hmm...
「あぁん❤そんなにがっついちゃダメだゾ❤」
"Don't be so eager, geez!"
「お宝より魅力的な”モノ”見つけちゃった…？」
"Found something more attractive than treasure...?"
いいじゃない❤
Isn't it nice?
誘うガーネットの赤
Inviting garnet red
極上の海賊の秘宝
The ultimate pirate's treasure
それは私
That is me
艶が溢れ漂う
Overflowing with allure
香りをどうかし怖がらないで
Don't be afraid of the scent
開けてみて
Open it up
sexy世界一
The sexiest in the world
superピチピチ
Super perky
ぶっちゃけ船長捕まえたいかなくない！？
Honestly, wouldn't you want to catch the captain!?
you're gonna get the treasure
maybe tasting me
私の甘さが欲しいでしょ
You want my sweetness, don't you?
秘宝の鍵を
The key to the treasure
優しく刺して
Gently insert it
宝庫の扉マジで早く開けて
Open the treasure vault door quickly
じれったい
Frustrating
貴方の手
Your hand
「やぁ、こんにちは」から始まる一日と
A day starting with "Hey, hello"
「こんばんは」で締めくくられる今日
And ending with "Good evening"
1. 付いて行く
1. Follow along
2. 逃げる
2. Run away
グルグル回っていく選択肢
Choices spinning round and round
そんな感じでいいんだよね？
That kind of vibe is fine, right?
どんなにスルーされても OK
It's OK no matter how much you get ignored
「こんなに…」なんてセリフは no OK
Lines like "So much..." are no OK
そんなに言われなくたって分かっているつもり…
As if I didn't know you'd say that...
君が流した涙で変身出来ちゃうの
You can transform with the tears you shed
「選んで生く」それだけじゃないでしょ？
It's not just about "choosing to live", is it?
ほら3つ数えたら笑うよ！「ハイ、チーズ！」
Come on, count to three and smile! "Hi, cheese!"
七色涙に乗る “レインボーダー”
"Rainbowder" riding on rainbow tears
「やぁ、こんにちは！ってあれっ！？」
"Hey, hello!" Wait, what!?
ちょっと置いてかないでよ、ねぇ！？
Don't leave me behind, hey!?
アタシ専用のフィルター！？
A filter just for me!?
1. ワンコール
1. One call
2. 通話中
2. On the call
神様って平等に不平等なものね
Gods are equally unequal
もっていたいなら散って
If you want to keep holding on, scatter
ってみたいならこっちおいで
If you want to try, come over here
妄想に衝動を被せだってほら
Covering impulses with delusions, look
妄想情動で誰になってね
Becoming someone in a delusional emotion
迷ってしまうのは誰のためね
Who are you getting lost for?
黙って逃げるのは気色悪せ
Running away silently is creepy
ずつずっふたりきりでアンコントロール
Uncontrolled, just the two of us step by step
きっときっとちゃんと全部交換しよう
Surely, let's exchange everything properly
回る baby don't stop
Spinning baby don't stop
ねえ ねえ 誰のせいかな
Hey, hey, whose fault is it?
あと 君の骨で
And with your bones
もっと ここでもだめですか
Is it still no good here?
いっぱいっぱいで乾杯だ
Filled to the brim, cheers to that
エコに踊ってみませんか
Won't you dance ecocly?
悩ましいから成長が
Troublesome growth
答えは そのうち出るかしら世界で
Will the answer come out soon in this world?
きっと 僕ら 刻々を6000センチしちゃってるの
Surely we're pacing 6,000 centimeters of time
回る baby don't stop
Spinning baby don't stop
守って痛いなら散って
If you want to protect and hurt, scatter
保ってほしいならこっちおいで
If you want me to keep it, come over here
冷静冷め目は放置しちゃって OK
Calm and cold eyes, leaving them be is OK
できえないなら要らないのよ
If you can't do it, I don't need it
気負ってしまうと過剰仕様じゃ
If you overexert yourself, it's over-spec
リミッター外して二人で出ないこんな
Removing limiters, stepping out together like this
ずつずっふたりきりでアンコントロール
Uncontrolled, just the two of us step by step
きっときっとちゃんと全部交換しよう
Surely, let's exchange everything properly
回る baby don't stop
Spinning baby don't stop
ねえ ねえ 誰のせいかな
Hey, hey, whose fault is it?
回る baby don't stop
Spinning baby don't stop
ねえ ねえ 君のせいだよ
Hey, hey, it's your fault
当たり前だそんなの何万回言われても同じ事
It's obvious, no matter how many times you say it
まったりめのこのモード I'm sick and tired of it
This laid-back mode, I'm sick and tired of it
“真っ逆さま墜ちろ”って言われても何も変わらないの
Even if you tell me to fall headfirst, nothing changes
大雑把だった何もかもお互いに勘違い
Everything was rough, mutual misunderstandings
信じ合うなんて何度目のこと
How many times have we tried to trust each other?
(Blowin') Walker, walker, walker, growling, s:
(Blowin') Walker, walker, walker, growling
Hey, walker, walker, walker
Walker, walker, walker, growling
Uh, Joohunnit One Hunnit, yah
Excuse me, I'm walkin' like zombie, uh
ボロボロの果て暴走して jumpin', uh
Running wild at the end of tatters, jumpin', uh
ギリギリの思慮に理性
On the verge of rationality and
感覚 blackout blackout
senses, blackout, blackout
塞めて記憶に刻んで 今を choppa, choppa
Carve it into memory, now, choppa, choppa
Block, block, block, can't block block
Your blah blah, stop talking, -ing
離れた感情だったら
If your emotions have drifted apart,
躊躇しないで pop, pop, pop
don't hesitate, pop, pop, pop
Never gonna stop this
僕を手放して go
Let go of me, go
君を縛った 想い出ごと drop
Drop the memories that bound you
彷徨い歩いても
Even if I wander around
無我夢中で探しても
Even if I search frantically
消えていくただ 幻想の姿
Only the illusory figure fades away
癒えない悲しみが
Unhealed sorrow
永遠にこの世界を止めるよ
Will stop this world forever
出口も終わりもない 闇ならいっそ
If it's a darkness with no exit or end
心へ shoot-out, shoot-out, shoot-out
Into the heart, shoot-out, shoot-out, shoot-out
壊して shoot-out, shoot-out, shoot-out
Break it, shoot-out, shoot-out, shoot-out
もう離れたいのなら
If you want to part ways already
戻れないのなら
If there's no turning back
希望なんかす見せないで
Don't show me any hope
心へ shoot-out, shoot-out, shoot-out
Into the heart, shoot-out, shoot-out, shoot-out
壊して shoot-out, shoot-out, shoot-out
Break it, shoot-out, shoot-out, shoot-out
また会おうなんて 言葉
Words like "let's meet again"
胸に刺さる
Pierce through my chest
ほらもっと深く
Come on, go deeper
愛なんて 逃げ道残して
Leave an escape route for love
終えをのみ規制するの
And strictly regulate it
琴線に触れ 感情に酔う言葉で
With words that touch the heart and intoxicate emotions
I hate you
蛾が火花へずに溺れて
Moths drown without seeing the sparks
自分がないなんて
To feel like you have nothing of your own
捨て去ればいい
You might as well throw it away
呆れるよ ねぇねぇ
It's pathetic, hey, hey
それでいいの
Is that really fine?
太陽で泳ぐ世界に 立ちあれど吐き捨てるの
Even in a world swimming in the sun, I spit it out
シャウト 君は忘れ潮よ 押しつけられる
Shout out, you're a receding tide, being pushed around
画策観に酔わされ 制御ばっか生きたくないわ
I don't want to live controlled by tactical illusions
夢語ってろよ
Keep talking about your dreams
Sick on the world
愛なんそして ひとり流した
If love is all it takes, then let's wash away alone
どんちゃの気分 自己犠牲のボケ
Silly moods and self-sacrificing fools
突破性野犬に笑うよ
Laughing at reckless stray dogs
事故成立かないで
Accident established, right?
Lion on the ground
I wanna shout out
息苦しいわ
It's so suffocating
愛の美しさね
The beauty of love...
ビス on the world
Vis on the world
幻想に揺り動かされる
Swayed by illusions
愛なんて 逃げ道残して
If love leaves an escape route
終えをのみ規制するの
And strictly regulates it
意味深な自己の男言葉で
With deep, self-centered words
I hate you, I hate you
蛾が火花へずに溺れて
Moths drown without seeing the sparks
預けた 心の鍵
Entrusted key of the heart
誰もがまっすぐなくすの
Everyone loses it straight away
嫌い人
Hated person
強制の針 縁浮かべ
Forced needles floating on the edge
街を行くの
Walking through the town
シャウト 君は忘れ潮よ
Shout out, you're a receding tide
押しつけられる画策感に
To the tactical feelings forced upon you
弱わ せいどん ばっか生きたくないわ
I don't want to live just controlled
夢語ってろよ
Keep talking about your dreams
Sick on the world
愛なんて それでいいのなら
If love is all it takes...
両親の快楽 飲み干すのロス
The loss of swallowing parents' pleasure
考えなしの ゲリに笑うよ
Laughing at thoughtless diarrhea
事故成立 かなんね
Accident established, right?
Lion on the ground
I wanna shout out
息苦しいわ
It's so suffocating
愛の美しさね
The beauty of love...
ビス on the world
Vis on the world
幻想に揺り動かされる
Swayed by illusions
愛なんて 逃げ道残して
If love leaves an escape route
終えをのみ規制するの
And strictly regulates it
意味深な自己の男言葉で
With deep, self-centered words
I hate you, I hate you
蛾が火花へずに溺れて
Moths drown without seeing the sparks
お疲れ様です！
Great job!
お疲れ様です！ お疲れ様！
Great job, thank you!
めちゃくちゃありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
この場合おめでとうございます。
Congratulations in this case!
白雪の方で もう本当にありがとうございます！
Noel-san, thank you so much!
てか一生！
For a lifetime!
今日何々チョコのさんチョコのさんの誕生日のためにさ、え？おめかししてくれたの？
Today, for Choco-san's birthday... huh? You dressed up?
ちょっと、そうですね。
Well, sort of.
ちょっとりささん以外では初めてお披露目しますね。
This is the first time showing it off outside of Risa-san's.
ちょっとちょっと！ 見て見て見て！
Hey, look, look, look!
カメラさん、足元から！ 主役ですよ、足元から！
Camera-san, from the feet! It's the main character, from the feet!
やめて！ やめて！
Stop it! Stop it!
本当に今日誕生日なのに...
Seriously, today is my birthday yet...
すげえかぶってる！
You're covering it all up!
なんかもう本当に呼んでいただけたことでもう嬉しいですけど、私の...
I'm glad just to be called on, but...
私のオリ曲歌って 一緒に踊ってくださって めっちゃ...
Singing my unit song and dancing together...
いやなんかもうめっちゃかっこいい曲やセクシーな...
Like, this is such a cool and sexy song!
いや私もチョコ先生バージョンが聴けて、まあの特に、え、ちょっと語っていいですか、あの...
I was so happy to hear Choco-sensei's version...
あの...ねえ、ねえがもう私...
Um, you know...
全然違う歌い方をされたので
Since you sang it in a totally different way,
えー すごいと思って
I thought it was amazing!
エチクッタって感じ。
It's kind of like...
ほかにもね、そう。あの、ありがと、チョコ先生バージョンも聴けて一緒に、しかもお披露目でできて嬉しいです。ありがとうございます。
Also, getting to hear Choco-sensei's version together on your debut stream makes me so happy. Thank you so much!
いやー、おめでとうございます。
Man, congratulations!
えー、じゃあさ、じゃあさ、きょうチョコちゃんの誕生日だから、チョコのお願い聞いてくれる？
Well then, since today is Choco-chan's birthday, will you grant Choco's request?
あ、なんでも、なんでもしますよ。靴舐めます。
Ah, I'll do anything! I'll lick your shoes!
いや、そういうことじゃない、そういうことじゃない。
No, that's not what I mean! That's not what I mean!
初めて言った。
First time saying that.
チョコ先生の、靴舐められるタイプですよ。
Choco-sensei is the type of person whose shoes get licked!
なんだら、今日もう、こんな素敵なものをプレゼントしてくれたなんて、なんでもしますよもう。
And today you gave me such a wonderful present, so I'll do anything!
え、じゃあさ、じゃあチョコをちょっと冷え性だから、巴様と
Well, since Choco has poor circulation, Tomoe-sama and...
一緒に写真撮りたい！
I want to take a photo together!
すごい！そんなのいつでも撮れますよ。
That's amazing! You can take photos anytime!
だってこんなエッチだと思えさまで、しかも3Dなんて、なかなかかわいいだよ、見て！
Because this is so erotic, Tomoe-sama, and it's 3D... it's so cute, look!
さっきまでの色気はすごいですよ、私。
Wait, your sexiness earlier was amazing.
チョコ先生もここ、ここめっちゃ...もう練習してたときからもう、ここ、あー...みたいな、あー...みたいな。
Choco-sensei, right here, right here... I was practicing like, "Ah..." "Ah..." like that!
すごい。こんなに、なんか本当にチョコ先生ってもうずっと応援させていただいてますけど、
Amazing! Truly, Choco-sensei, I've always been supporting you, but...
色っぽいのに、そのかわいいおちゃめなところもたくさんあって本当に、あ、写真でしたっけ？
You're sexy, but you also have so many cute moments! Wait, was it a photo?
うち撮るんです。撮りましょう！お写真、お写真！
Let's take one! Photos, photos!
どんなポーズがみんな、いいんだろ。
Every pose is good, right?
えっとさ、あの、背中合わせでパンチしたい。はい、はねー！はねかわいいね！おはねー！
Um, let's do a back-to-back punch! Wow, so cute!
結構身長差ありますね、私たち。ね、ともえさん？
We have quite a height difference, don't we? Yeah. Tomoe-san?
うん。
Yeah.
身長おいくつなんですか？私ヒール込みで178なんですio。
How tall are you? I'm 178 cm in heels!
すごい、なんかいつも、ホロライブさんのライブとかね、大きから、ちょこごんめっちゃでかいからいつも、そうそうそうそう。
Amazing! Whenever we do 3D lives, Choco-san is so tall, and I'm always so small.
なんかすごい。天使天使、かわいいしね。ちっちゃいちょこせんもかわいいですね。
So, look, I look like a fairy, and tiny Choco-sen is so cute too!
私と並べると、うれしい。じゃあ、背中合わせで、背中合わせで。うん、うん。いい感じ、いい感じ。
With us side by side... Yay, how cute!
ほら、みんな！スクショタイムだぞー！
Alright everyone, it's screenshot time!
パチン、パチンなんだ。
It's a peace sign!
あの、背中合わせで立ったの、と、ともえさんか、ピストルしてるやつ。そう、すごく好き。え、ありがとうございます。
Um, standing back-to-back like this, Tomoe-san, this finger-point pose... I love it so much! Thank you!
撮れたー？撮れた？
Did you take it? Did you take it?
じゃあそっから上を、腕を上にして、セクシーポーズ。ばっちり。
Then from there, arms up high, and a sexy pose! Perfect!
お、いいの！すごい！めっちゃいいの！今日、きょにゅうときょにゅうが並んでますよ！すごいことになってるもう。ビッグなんですよ。
Oh, nice! That's amazing! Our heights are lined up! This is huge!
すごいですね！あー、うれしい！すごい、ありがとうございます、なんか。
Amazing! Yay, I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
え、え、え、あとさ、あとさ。
Um, let's see, what else? What else?
じゃあ、ちょっと、セクシー。あ、いいよ。いらっしゃい。
Shall we sit down a bit? Sexy pose. Ah, okay, sure.
えい、えい。えい、なんだ？うんうん。こう？手が動いとる。ピカピカ。うん、口？
Let's sit like this. What kind of pose? Cross? Hands moving? Peeking? Lips?
あー！すごい！うわ、かわいい！なんか私の方がサキュバスっぽいね、一生的に。
Ah, amazing! So cute! Somehow, mine looks more like a succubus, right?
かわいい天使、かわいい！かわいい天使！
Cute angel, cute! Cute angel!
え、めちゃかわいいです。
So cute!
あー、めっちゃ絵になるー！うれしい！え、かわいい！
Ah, it's becoming so artistic! I'm so happy! So cute!
にっこり。いやもう本当、この並べる日が来るなんて、3Dで、うれしいです。うれしい。
Smiling! I'm really so happy we can do this 3D day together!
ありがとうございます。いいか、撮れたかな？撮れたかな？ね。
Thank you so much. Did we get it? Did we get it?
いっしょ。
Let's get up.
あーー！いや、本当に、おめでとうございます、もう。
Ah, truly congratulations!
え、あ、ありがと。チョコ先生の誕生日なのを、私がなんかもう、とっておきの忘れられない。
Even though it's Choco-sensei's birthday, I'll never forget this!
もう誕生日、私も今日を誕生日にしたいぐらいですよ、もう。
Today's birthday... I want to make today my birthday too!
えー、本当に！本当に、ありがとうございます！
Eh, really? Thank you so much!
え、でも今日は歌って踊れて、すごい、嬉しかった。
Today we sang and danced, I'm so happy!
本当こちらこそです、本当に、あの、頑張ってください、これからも、応援してておりますので。ありがとうございます！
Tomoe-san, please keep doing your best! I'll keep supporting you from now on too! Thank you!
では、ありがとうございました！めちゃくちゃ楽しかったです！ありがとうございました！
Then, thank you very much! It was so much fun! Thank you very much!
ちょっと待って、どこ行くの？え？
Wait, Tomoe-san, where are you going? Eh?
え？え、ん？お？何ですか？
Eh? What is it?
ちょっともう、せっかくなら、最前列で見ようと思って。
Wait, since it's a rare chance, let's look at it from the very front!
待って、待って、待って。
Wait, wait, wait!
袖で、袖で見てましたけど、もう、もう、前で見たいと思ってたんで。
Wait, I've been watching from the sleeves, but I want to watch from the front!
チョコ様は、チョコメイトたちにそんな、もう、興奮されちゃうから。あ、ちょっと待って、前で見せてよ！
Choco-sensei, you get so excited before Choco-mate shows! But wait, I want to watch from the front too!
チョコ様はこっち！
Choco-sama is over here!
そう、チョウチョ、チョウチョになってるから、チョウチョになってるから。
Because it's turning into a butterfly, once it turns into a butterfly...
いいから、歌いなさい！
Go on and sing!
はい、ということで。いやあ、ガチでみんな、チョコ様はめちゃめちゃエッチ的で素敵だったよ！
And with that... Seriously everyone, Choco-sama is super, super ecchi and wonderful!
あー！
Ah!
ちょこちゃんのね、お誕生日記念ガチャ引いてきてくれました、ということで！
Choco-chan's birthday gacha has been rolled, so!
続いてはね、ちょっとちょこかっこよくなっちゃおうかな、ということで！
Next up, let's make Choco look a little cool, so!
次の曲は、
The next song is...
まあちょこのね、今年のテーマというか、
Well, as for Choco's theme this year, so to speak,
ビラン、聞いてください。
Please listen to "Villain."
きっと手を繋ぐだけでゾッとするされる
I'm sure just us holding hands will make them horrified
馬鹿けた競争一抜けたら通報される
Once you count yourself outta the rat race, you get reported
突然変異じゃない ただの僕さ XとかYとか
I'm not a mutant; I'm just me, X or Y or whatever
べき論様は善悪多頭飼い 僕が君を侵略するって言いふらしてる
Those imposing their views keep saying I'm "infringing" you
Oh Mr.Crazy Villain Villain 夜行性の花弁
Oh Mr. Crazy Villain Villain, nocturnal petals
違う服着て君の前では 男子のフリする
I dress differently and pretend to be a boy in front of you
拝啓 Dr. Durand-Durand 迎えにきてください
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand, please come pick me up
顔も知らない誰かにとって 僕はもうヴィラン
For someone who doesn't know my face, I'm already a villain
蛇蝎ライフ 蛇蝎ライフ
Detested life, detested life
挙句の果ての爛れ
Eventually corrupting
逸脱の性をまた日々隠す
Covering up my deviant nature day by day
雄蘂と雄蘂じゃ立ち行かないの?
Can't get anywhere with stamen and stamen?
ねえ知ってんのか 乱歩という作家のことを
Hey, do you know a writer called Ranpo?
import you import you
造花も果ては実を結ぶ
Even artificial flowers will bear fruit someday
ぶるってんじゃねーよ 多種多様の性
Don't be so afraid, there are so many genders
悲しい悲しい話をしようか ゼラチン質の「で?」
Shall we tell a sad, sad story? A gelatinous "So what?"
Mr.Crazy Villain Villain 可能性に幸あれ
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain, all the best to your possibilities
僕のハートは1LDK 嫉妬くらいはさせてよ
My heart's a 1LDK apartment, let me at least be jealous
Hi there もっとーYOLO YOLO 微熱愛でいいのに
Hi there, my motto's YOLO YOLO, a slight feverish love would do
誰も知らない 知られたくない 皮膚の下
Nobody knows, and I don't want them to know, under my skin
素晴らしい悪党共々に捧げる讃歌
A hymn dedicated to wonderful scoundrels
骨まで演じ切ってやれ悪辣に
Play the role to the bone, viciously
残酷な町ほど綺麗な虹が立つ
The crueler the town, the more beautiful the rainbow
猥雑広告に踊るポップ体の愛
Dancing to vulgar adverts, a pop font love
Oh Mr.Crazy Villain Villain 夜行性の花弁
Oh Mr. Crazy Villain Villain, nocturnal petals
違う服着て君の前では 男子のフリを
I dress differently and pretend to be a boy in front of you
拝啓 Dr. Durand-Durand ここだよ
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand, right here
顔も知らない誰かにとって 僕はもうヴィラン
For someone who doesn't know my face, I'm already a villain
ヴィラン ヴィラン
Villain, villain
ヴィラン ヴィラン ヴィラン ヴィラン
Villain, villain, villain, villain
蛇蝎ライフ 蛇蝎ライフ 挙句の果てのヴィラン
Detested life, detested life, in the end, a villain
はい、ということで、みなさま！
Yes, so everyone!
ちょこの重代告知、1つ目、今年もあります！
Choco's major announcement, number one, is happening this year too!
どうぞー！
Ta-da!
結城ちょこ誕生日記念グッズ！まずは詳細を見ていきましょう、こちら！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Commemoration Goods! First let's check the details, here!
どうぞ、Nardack先生描き下ろし！アクリルジオラママスタンド！
Ta-da, drawn by Nardack-sensei! Acrylic diorama stand!
ということでね、今回はNardack先生に描き下ろしていただきました！めちゃめちゃ良くないですか、こちらのジオラママスタンドなんです。みんな飾れ！
So, this time Nardack-sensei drew this for us! Isn't it super nice, this diorama stand. Everyone display it!
そして2つ目は、こちら！ちょこの悪魔スウェット！ということでね、こちらなんと
And the second one is, here! Choco's devil sweatshirt! So, this actually...
ワンポイント胸元にチョコメイト。
A Chocomate logo embroidered on the chest.
そしてね、背面にはナルダック先生のめちゃめちゃおしゃれなイラストが！
And on the back, an amazingly stylish illustration by Nardack-sensei!
これはちょこのスウェットを、おしゃれで普段着以外にも切れちゃうんじゃない？
This Choco sweatshirt is so stylish you can wear it out casually too, right?
そしてそして、
And then, and then...
たーだーん！皆さん、お待たせいたしました！
Ta-da! Everyone, thanks for waiting!
これ欲しかったんじゃないんですか？
Isn't this what you've all been wanting?
魔導書風ポストカード……あ、間違えちゃった。魔導書風ポストカードアルバム！
A grimoire-style postcard... Ah, I messed up. A grimoire-style postcard album!
ということで、みんなね、記念グッズとか買うときにポストカードいっぱい溜まってるでしょ？
So, you know how everyone accumulates lots of postcards when buying commemorative goods?
ちょこがアルバム作ってやったから、そこの中にいっぱいしまって、後でいっぱい見返しして。
Choco made an album for you, so you can store them all in there and look back at them anytime.
はい、そして、
Yes, and then...
今年もあります。
It's available this year too.
ュブちょこ勝ち下ろし台本耳舐めASMR！
Newly recorded ASMR with ear-licking scripts by Yubuchoco!
こちらね、ボイス3種類ございます。
There are three types of voice tracks here.
まず1つ目のボイスは、ちょこ姉の殿尻いじわるボイスということで、
First up is "Choco-nee's Teasing Voice," where...
はい。いや、こちらはね、ちょこがちょっと殿尻しながら、ちょっとイタズラしちゃうんだよね。
Right. Well, in this one, Choco teases you while acting a bit mischievous.
そしてそして、ちょこ先生の秘密の課外授業ということで、
And then, "Choco-sensei's Secret Extracurricular Lesson," where...
まあみんなはね、ちょっとおサボりしてる、ちょっと生徒さんになっていただいて、ちょこ先生と秘密の課外授業をしちゃうっていうえっちえっちボイス。
you become a lazy student and end up having a secret, naughty extracurricular lesson with Choco-sensei—a very lewd voice track.
そして、最後、診断のちょこボイスはね、こちらなんとちょっとね、時間も長めのちょっと耳舐めプラスちょっといろんなものもリダくさんのえっちえっちボイスなので、まあちょっとね、楽しみにして聞いててください。
And lastly, "The Ultimate Choco Voice" is a longer ear-licking track packed with lots of other goodies, so please look forward to listening to it!
そして、フルセットの特典は、こちら！
And the full set bonus is... right here!
たーだーん！
Ta-da!
なんと今回、久しぶりにちょっと数量限定の直筆サイン＆複製メッセージ入りポストカードが、直筆サイン複製メッセージ入り、直筆サイン先生勝ち下ろしポストカードがついてくる！
This time, for the first time in a while, it comes with a quantity-limited postcard featuring a handwritten autograph and duplicated message, and a freshly drawn postcard by Nardack-sensei!
こちらね、数量限定なので、さ、皆様、今回は頑張ってください！
Since this is in limited quantities, everyone, please do your best this time!
早めに、早めにお願いします！
Early, please get it early!
そして、特典2つ目は、あの皆さまがちょこのペットになっていただいて、ちょこ先生に飼われてみたらどうなっちゃうの？みたいな、ちょっとASMRボイスを撮ってみました！
And the second bonus is an ASMR voice track where you become Choco's pet and find out what happens when you get kept by Choco-sensei!
お楽しみに！はい、こちらね、通常、通常版は、あのちょこのね、サインとメッセージがちょっと箔押しのね、複製メッセージ複製サインになってしまうのですが、その他の特典は変わらないので、はい、皆様、
Look forward to it! Yes, in the regular edition, Choco's autograph and message are foil-stamped duplicated versions, but the other bonuses remain the same, so everyone...
全力で頑張れ！
Give it your all!
はい、ということで、こちらね、ライブ終了後に関売開始となりますので、皆様待機しといてください。
Yes, so sales for this will start after the live ends, so everyone please standby for it.
そして、この後は、皆様おまちかね、レッドカーペット、いくぞー！
And after this, everyone's long-awaited... RED CARPET! Let's go!
毎年これ、ちょこの誕生日にはこれが欠かせないよねということで、今年もやります、レッドカーペット！
As always, this is an absolute must for Choco's birthday, so we're doing it again this year: RED CARPET!
まあまあまあまあ、このレッドカーペットをご存知でない方は、今回初めてだよって方、はーい！
Well, for those of you who don't know what this Red Carpet is, or if this is your first time, raise your hand!
ちょっとご説明させていただきます。まあでもね、俺、知ってるぜって方は、どうぞ。
Let me explain a bit. Well, for those of you who say "I already know," go ahead.
ということで、みんな、見えるかな、今ね、みんなに慣れてもらったものがなんと、じゃーんと、ちょこがね、この先の告知への道を作ってくれますということで、
So everyone, can you see? What everyone has gotten used to now is... ta-da! Choco will pave the way for future announcements, so...
わあ、みんな、ありがとう！
Wow, everyone, thank you!
では、早速進んでいきましょう！
Now then, let's get right into it!
はい、ということで、今回この新ステージもね、ちょこのこのお誕生日のライブのために作っていただきました！
Yes, so this new stage was also made specially for Choco's birthday live!
めちゃめちゃ良くないですか、このステージ！そしてね、なんと……
Isn't this stage amazingly nice? And also, amazingly...
今回のサムネも
In this sub as well,
まあね
well...
毎年お世話になっているあんばさ先生に描いていただきました！
Amubasa-sensei, who takes care of me every year, drew this for me!
わあー！わあ！
Yay! Wow!
ということでね、めちゃめちゃエッチでしょう？
So, isn't it super lewd?
そう、禁断の果実食べてる感。
Yeah, that forbidden fruit vibe.
いいでしょ、いいでしょー！
Isn't it great? Isn't it great?!
なんとね、この後も重大告知があります！
And guess what, there's a big announcement after this too!
いやーもうみんなね、楽しみにしてると思うんだけど。
Man, I'm sure you're all looking forward to it.
ちょこもね、早くね、お披露目したくてうずうずしてるよ。
Choco is getting all impatient to show it off early too.
ま、今回ね、ちょっとグッズの方も通常限定なっているので、皆様、早めに買っといてね、ということで。
Well, this time, the merch is also limited/regular, so everyone, be sure to buy it early!
えーと、せーの、よん！ありがとー！
Um, ready, set, four! Thank you!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ということでね、今回重大告知、第2弾はー！
So, for this big announcement, the 2nd part is...
今回も、ちょこグッズ買っちゃいました！
This time too, I bought Choco merch!
禁断の果実テーマの、ありきゅー！
The forbidden fruit-themed... akyu!
世界一セクシーでかっこいいガチャを揃えたいと思います！
I want to put together the sexiest and coolest gacha in the world!
このね、新曲が終わったらなんと新曲のMV公開とメンバー限定ライブもあるので、皆様メンバーシップのご加入よろしくお願いします！
Once this new song ends, there will be a new song MV release and a member-only live, so everyone, please join the membership!
それでは行きましょうか。
Well then, shall we go?
人ばかりの光
In the light crowded with people,
月明かりの代わり
replacing the moonlight,
見下ろした街並み
the cityscape I look down upon
少しも惹かれない
doesn't appeal to me at all.
嗅ぎつけてよ気持ち
Can you sense my feelings?
この時間も惜しい
Even this moment is precious.
焦らすのも嗜み
Teasing is also a skill,
そういうの今度でいい？
so how about it next time?
Guilty Pleasure
蜜もっと飲ませて
let me drink more of the nectar,
もっと言わせて「恥ずかしい」
let me say more, "It's embarrassing."
君はどこにでもいる Boy
You're just like any other boy,
なのに胸がヒリつく Why?
yet my heart races, why?
いけるところまでいかせて
Let me go as far as I can,
揺れる輪郭もう湿ってる Got Cheat
the trembling contours are already damp, got cheat.
これはありふれている Lick
This is commonplace, just a lick,
だけど繰り返したい Words
but I want to repeat these words.
いけるところまでいかせて
Let me go as far as I can,
甘い誘惑 癖になってる Got Cheat
sweet temptations have become a habit, got cheat.
Oh 君のせいでも僕のせいでも
Oh, whether it's your fault or mine,
Oh どちらでも Got Cheat
oh, it doesn't matter, got cheat.
確かめてよ相性
Confirm our compatibility,
ただ求めて欲しい
I just want you to desire me.
バレるまで過ち
Until we're caught in our mistakes,
余所見はしないでいい？
let's not look away, okay?
Guilty Pleasure
棘もっと這わせて もっと先まで
let me crawl further with the thorns, even further.
Guilty Pleasure
鍵もっと回して もっと言わせて「こじ開けて」
turn the key more, let me say more, "Open it up."
僕を慰めている Toy
You comfort me like a toy,
思考焼き切れるまで High
until my thoughts are burned out, high.
いけるところまでいかせて
Let me go as far as I can,
熟れる禁断 そう破ってる Got Cheat
breaking the ripened taboo, that's what I'm doing, got cheat.
君はどこにでもいる Boy
You're just like any other boy,
You're anywhere, Boy
なのに胸がヒリつく Why?
Yet my heart stings, Why?
いけるところまでいかせて
Let me go as far as I can
揺れる輪郭もう湿ってる
My trembling contours are already damp
Got Cheat
これはありふれている Lick
This is commonplace, Lick
だけど繰り返したい Words
But I want to repeat these words
いけるところまでいかせて
Let me go as far as I can
甘い誘惑 癖になってる Got Cheat
Sweet temptation has become a habit, Got Cheat
君のせいでも 僕のせいでも
Whether it's your fault or my fault,
Oh どちらでも
Oh, either way,
Oh 何度でも Got Cheat
Oh, no matter how many times, Got Cheat
はい、ということで、皆さま！
Alright, everyone!
この後は MVプラス温泉ライブ楽しみましょー！
Look forward to the MV + Hot Springs Live after this!
それでは、合図で、レッツゴー！
Now then, on my signal, let's go!
あ、勝手に飛ばされるんで大丈夫だよそのままで、いってらっしゃい！
Ah, it'll skip automatically so it's fine just as you are, have a good one!